prettygalz.com 2019-06-09

# PrettyGalz.com Privacy Policy - PrettyGalz.com

**Privacy Policy**

 **PrettyGalz.com Privacy Policy**  
This statement covers the site  
[www.PrettyGalz.com](http://www.prettygalz.com/) (PrettyGalz.com).

Please read this statement carefully before using or proceeding to access PrettyGalz.com. Your use of PrettyGalz.com indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

 **Information Collection**  
PrettyGalz.com is the sole owner of the information collected on [www.PrettyGalz.com](http://www.prettygalz.com/).  
PrettyGalz.com may collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

 **Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of this Web site, users can choose to leave  
comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must  
submit information including a valid email address. PrettyGalz.com uses this  
information to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and  
conditions of use, and will not pass this information to any other organization.

 **Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example,  
advertisers). However, PrettyGalz.com has no access to or control over these  
cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.  
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by PrettyGalz.com only and  
does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
The advertisements appearing on PrettyGalz.com are delivered to users by  
Google, among other services. Information about user’s visit to this site, such  
as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or  
any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

 **Log Files**  
Like most standard Website servers we use log files. This includes internet  
protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP),  
referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to  
analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and  
gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are  
not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility  
that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, PrettyGalz.com may  
need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a  
good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current  
judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Website.

 **Business Transitions**  
In the event PrettyGalz.com goes through a business transition, such as a  
merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets,  
user’s personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets  
transferred.

 **Links**  
PrettyGalz.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we,  
PrettyGalz.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other  
sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read  
the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally  
identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information  
collected by PrettyGalz.com.

 **Notification of Changes**  
Whenever PrettyGalz.com changes our privacy policy, we will post those  
changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our  
users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under  
what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please  
contact us at Admin **at** PrettyGalz.com.
